How are you guys doing? I'm back.
I was just here to fresh start.
Make sure there's a little bit too much.
Hey Schmalley, what's up? We're back. I'm good. It looks like the
And then the separate icons, the member icons on the little side chat, it's pretty cool.
I never noticed that.
Remember, it's only emojis, how I wanted to do this, ASAP.
If anybody knows any graphic, you know,
I don't think SAS is really buggy with me anymore.
If anyone knows how to do some simple emojis,
simple graphics, put it to the emoji size,
I can give you the specifications.
I like to have some cats, some tarot cards,
and maybe like a beat-ahead,
or I don't know,
we're gonna have different people that are on the show,
I don't know.
No.
DJ Electra, I'll ask Electra when she,
I'll ask Electra,
because yeah, she might be able to help out.
Love Electra.
Smelly's a member of Schmelly. Thank you for being here
Good to see you hopefully everyone's doing good
You've losing my likes well, it's okay, you know
I know I just
You know, I don't want to take any risks
They try to protect this channel
But that's the audio wasn't too good and I was you know, I need a fresh start
But bro, it's all good some stuff is just lost to the ether
There are websites you can go grab already mate emojis and use them to get for discord, okay?
Just have to make sure that they're all legit for me to use. Yeah, I'll check it out
Yeah, I do need to upload some emojis in there
How does it just work anymore?
Yeah
Yeah, yeah guys if you could help me out with that. Yeah, it sucks to research sometimes now. It's you know
Some people can't find don't won't see the next lab come up
but
Maybe it I don't know
Let's do a psalm. I love doing psalms 17th string. No, it's only number two
some
The short one I like more the psalms
Some 72
of Solomon, okay?
Endow the king with your justice, O God, the royal son with your righteousness. May he judge your people in righteousness.
Your afflicted ones with justice. May the mountains bring prosperity to the people. The hills
The fruit of righteousness. May he defend the afflicted among people and save the children of the needy.
May he crush the oppressor. May he endure as long as the sun, as long as the moon through all generations.
May he be like rain falling on a moon field, like showers watering the earth.
In his days may the righteous flourish, and prosperity abound till the moon is no more.
May he rule from sea to sea, and from the river to the ends of the earth.
May the desert tribes bow before him and his enemies lick his dust.
May the kings of Tarshish and of distant shores be tribute to him.
May the kings of Sheba and Siba present him gifts.
May all kings bow down to him and all nations serve him.
For he will deliver the needy who cry out, the afflicted who have no one to help.
He will take pity on the weak and the needy and save the needy from death.
He will rescue from oppression and violence.
For precious is their blood in his sight. Long may he live, may gold from Sheba be given him,
may people ever pray for him, and bless him all day long, may grain abound throughout the land,
on tops of the hills may it sway, may the crops flourish like Lebanon, and thrive like the grass
in the field, may his name endure forever, may it continue as long as the sun. Then all nations
will be blessed through him, and they will call him blessed.
Praise to be to the Lord God the God of Israel who alone does marvelous deeds
Praise be his glorious name forever. May the whole earth be filled with his glory. Amen. Amen.
Yeah, do you ever hear be this age you would
Yeah, I'm just all I might have heard that
W. Yeah, you can smoke outside. Yeah
So that was a nice little little song
The dog
No, that's my food food coming
Do you love anal bleachings? Oh
It's my food is shouldn't take too long McDonald's I mean
Oh, it's on its way, almost here.
I guess it's still at the McDonald's a few minutes away.
What would you do if J-Dog and I slept in the same bed?
I don't know.
He might have to sleep with what I open.
So wait on the cooking stream.
Yeah, I got to clean out my kitchen a little bit.
and you cook something.
Do you want some details?
I don't know.
I don't think JDogg wants me to describe
my fantasies with him.
I make him a little bit uncomfortable.
Maybe I'll just
give him a hug.
We'd have a sheet between us.
So it wouldn't be gay.
There would be no skin.
So Wendy says a new talkie, oh, where's the cover?
So Wendy says a new talkie's Fuego chicken sandwich.
Have you ever tried that?
Can you model for a steaky?
Jada wants to do that ass shake?
Oh my gosh.
Do you saw a recorded woman in the shower?
That's not good.
I could do better than Jada.
Oh yeah, maybe.
I don't know. I hit on J-Dog. He gave me very far. He doesn't even play back.
I like if you'll play back a little. You know Joker played back and
some people play back. It's like you see Ty was already tried. He persuaded you to
do it with him over you. Oh guys, don't fight over me, you know. I'm no catch.
Mess.
You have to be whiteboarders and book planning. Yeah, good idea
Big whiteboard. Yeah
Well, I've been doing I've been doing drawings of people, you know
So Doug if you'd like me to draw you and draw you today
It's just tobacco, it's smoking.
Time never said anything about itself.
Who'd you, who'd you, who'd you just, who'd you just talking to?
Doug, he was going me that?
My caucus is laughing
I guess they sneak to see me
Yeah, well, I'm glad I'm on it some people
Yeah, I mean he's he's banned
No, I didn't but I just want to be careful
All good
Do we hit the red X for a reason?
well
Now Nick didn't really show it wasn't much you just showed the top of his butt, but I
Don't know. I don't people like people like trying to strike for that
Our answer for you I could I know I know that I know good times list losses show
What am I drinking on? Nothing yet. I'm getting a couple of coffee. They're on their way. They should be here any minute.
Oh, it's delivered. I'll be right back.
Okay
Yeah, let me sure it was fine and his you got mad at me he said I treat my guests like garbage, I don't
Hi, babe
Hi, babe. Let's see Lola.
Hi, babe.
Oh, good for you, JMFC. Congratulations. I think that's awesome. Hi, babe.
Hi, baby.
Oh, baby, baby.
Oh, baby, baby. How was I supposed to know?
Something wasn't right.
Oh, baby, baby. I shouldn't have let you down.
Yeah
Congratulations
Everyone's a mod except for like, you know, I have like Jamie's Cowboys is the I
Have he was covered as a mod, but there's too many people
being
attacked as
Mods for people like, you know timing people out and everyone was always going after them. So
Hi, babe.
So tricks, two tricks, one tricks.
No, hey, Nancy.
Jamie's been with me since the beginning of my show.
She's a very good greeter.
Good
Hi Nancy, hi everybody
Yeah, the mod is like really like it's really it's better not to be a mod
You like the title well, we'll see if I add mods if uh
It's your motto. I should have you to change your name for good reason. Yeah
Yes, thank you Amber too
Hi, babe
Yeah
It's pretty interesting being a gay person on a on YouTube. I don't see that many that many
or I certainly don't see very many that are running open panels
and so in this universe and so it's just interesting how
yeah ready for McDonald's french fries I know Tristan's just so cozy right now you're so cozy
But, yeah, anybody else seen anybody else talk?
I think people are already, you know,
Arthur's like, oh, yeah, so, you know,
Eldo and Sandman aren't coming over anymore.
They said they were talking about me.
Another Kate's are talking about me.
And if you can tune a helper,
I think I'm going to get my fries out.
Oh, I'll put some fries.
Got a small fry, so I'll eat them while they're hot.
Right?
Yeah, but fuck, I'm not gonna get to you.
Okay
Let's see you guys your salmon or I'll say they promote your channel. Have you not heard that? I don't know
He said it was on some kind of a
Instead it was on a discord they were talking about
I'm not sure I kind of left all those discords
I'll get my link pinned
Okay, we're watching Nick.
We're watching some yard work.
Oh my gosh.
You see a man's boyfriend
Yeah, ever yeah, all you guys were good mods. I like I loved his mods. I just have
So my mods are being targeted
people were being
We're like complaining about
Not being my or begging for wrenches and stuff like that. So I just simplified it
I'll consider remodding some people as we go on
Just see if I don't have a mod in the room
Yeah, very creative his boyfriend Ray Ray is in prison. Oh
Damn any of boyfriend him Ray Ray
Now, it looks like he's in fast motion, because he's on a better motion.
So, it's serious. His boyfriend is in Rikers.
The fries are good
Running up it's a joke
He has a patchy cat who's a guy named Ray Ray
Can I come under the blanket with me?
Come on babe.
Hi babe.
Thank you, it's kind of faded a little bit
If you know a little bit
Thank you, Jim next
Thank you, I'm my babe over here
My tricks
Hi, Mr. Frixie.
Hey, not to say a man's female
Trolls
Your color is pink
Hi, hey rude, hey rude, my rude, rude over there
So what happened so Kate was bullying or Kate was bullying Jim Nick. I don't know if that's is that the real Jim Nick in the chat
There's a fake gimmick, I'm not sure
Doug D can't tell if it's real or fake
Jamie if you click on their name Jim Nick and then go to the channel and see if they when they created the channel and if there's any content
You can do that. That'd be awesome
Hi, I had lovely bubs lovely rubber
I have over 100 chair decks.
By the way, it sent me a picture of your stock file.
Oh, wow.
It's a lot.
What's your favorite deck?
I have many decks.
Oh, here it goes.
She called me a drunk wet brain.
Oh, I don't know. Yeah, they're over there saying, oh, he's on drugs. He's doing this. He's doing that.
Oh, okay, Jim.
Oh, God.
Gay people do drugs?
Sometimes.
Ah.
Maybe, you know.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Uh-uh
No, uh, Susan, it's a fake me.
That's good.
How's everyone doing in chat? Just hanging out. I guess nobody wants to come up in chat.
It's been a little bit quiet like that. Brother came up. Michael L came up. Christine came up.
Now Nick's here, but
slow down.
I'm trying to do the best
I guess I can do. Let me see. Oh, look at it. It's tearing down that hole.
It's got a hacksaw.
Piling up the bushes we're watching some IRL yard work guys
Not at all he man. I don't know. I'm sorry. I
Don't know. You're fine. I'm sorry if I didn't respond. Do you say something? I'm kind of missing my comments
This is but wow the next breeze coming in today
Okay juice, no what did Kate say? What's going on? I
Don't know how Kate would know anything about my dad
Think she did something she sent me condolences and then the day you passed away
Oh
Choose just go to my hit the stream our link just go to the back private chat and you can tell me there
Isn't that big eyes? Isn't that like pretty low? It's like
Father's passed away. She's gonna say anything about him
Yeah, guys, I think she's making fun of him being dead
Now isn't that like just like disgusting
Hi, Lenore Lenore, there's Lenore
My dad was a great man. There's nothing there's nothing bad there can be said about him
Hey, if you're the nor come here one the nor come on
Nor
Come on, take that.
Lenora, come on.
Come on, babe.
You know, it's a little happy cat.
It's a little cold today.
A little bit of a breeze.
But we are happy to do these.
Yeah, I don't know.
I haven't been on their show. I've just been on my show. I'm not talking about them. I don't know why
I feel like they need to attack me and slander me but
Yeah, it's like
Yeah
Yeah, my dad that's that was a
Very awesome guy. Hey, babe. Come on here with me
I'm babe
Hi
It's okay
Okay, man that a gay man can pull or superman that you can
Thank you guys
Okay guys, I'm just gonna leave Nick on the screen for a little bit, if you don't want to come up, I'm listening.
Um
Thanks for watching and I'll see you in the next video.
Thank you.
I had afternoon's afternoon sleep stream
Hello afternoon sleep stream
How are we doing guys
I'll be back later.
Sorry about that.